近在眼前了
Alright, just a few more feet.
到了  同志们
And... here we are, gentlemen,
黑暗之门
The gates of elzebob.
上帝保佑
Good lord.
沉住气  97小时的鏖战就为了这一刻
Don't panic. this is what the last 97 hours have been about.
站着别动  那有一大群拿着武器的地精
Stay frosty. there's a horde of armed goblins
艾泽拉斯之剑就在门的另一边
On the other side of that gate guarding the sword of asaroth.
战士们  拿出你们的武器  法师们  举起你们的魔杖
Warriors, unsheathe your weapons. magic wielders, raise your wands.
各就各位
Lock and load.
拉杰  把门给轰开
Raj, blow the gates.
轰了大门
Blowing the gates.
Ctrl
Control,
SHIFT... B
Shift... b!
天哪  这么多地精
Oh, my god, so many goblins!
别傻愣着啊  打起来  跑起来
Don't just stand there, slash and move!
保持阵型
Stay in formation!
里奥纳德  你背后有个怪
Leonard, you got one on your tail.
背后偷袭也没用...我会干掉他的
My tail's prehensile-- I'll swat him off.
我得手了  里奥纳德
I got him, leonard.
今晚我要和着地精的鲜血痛饮一番
Tonight I spice my mead with goblin blood.
拉杰  那是个陷阱  他们想夹击我们
Raj, no, it's a trap! they're flanking us!
他打中我了
He's got me!
谢尔顿  他击中拉杰了  你快用昏迷术
Sheldon, he's got raj. use your sleep spell!
我拿到艾泽拉斯之剑了
I've got the sword of asaroth!
别管那剑了  快去帮拉杰
Forget the sword, help raj!
我才不是什么谢尔顿  我是剑圣
There is no more sheldon. I am the sword master!
-里奥纳德  当心  -靠  我们要被团灭了
- leonard, look out! - damn it, man, we're dying here!
再见了  各位乡巴佬
Good-bye, peasants!
那小杂种自己开了传送门跑了
The bastard teleported!
他在易趣上出售了那把剑
He's selling the sword of asaroth on ebay.
你为钱出卖了我们?  你到底是谁?
You betrayed us for money? who are you?
我是暗夜精灵盗贼
I'm a rogue night elf.
没读过游戏的人物介绍吗
Don't you people read character descriptions?
等等  刚刚有人点了购买
Wait, wait! somebody just clicked "buy it now."
我才是剑圣
I am the sword master!
我浑身都是汗
I'm all sweaty.
有谁想去第二人生游泳吗
Anybody want to log on to second life and go swimming?
我刚造了个虚拟泳池
I just built a virtual pool.
不  我现在不想看到你  或你的化身
No. I can't look at you or your avatar right now.
好像你的邻居回来了
Sounds like your neighbor's home.
失陪下
Excuse me.
别忘了你故意不小心拿错的信
Don't forget the mail you took accidentally on purpose
那可是你和她搭讪的借口
As an excuse to talk to her.
对  对  对
Oh, right, right, right.
信件劫掠者  -很老套  不过我喜欢
Stealing snail mail-- very old school. I like it.
潘妮  那个邮差又送错...
Penny, the mailman, did it again...
对不起
Sorry.
嗨  里奥纳德  这是道格
Hi, leonard. this is doug.
道格  这是我邻居里奥纳德
Doug, this is my neighbor leonard.
什么事  老兄?
What's up, bro?
没什么...
Not much...
老兄...
Bro.
有事吗
Is everything okay?
是的  没  只是  你的信又跑我这来了
Yeah, no, I just... I got your mail again. here.
谢谢  我已经和那邮差说过了
Thank you. I've got to talk to that mailman.
噢  不  那样不太好吧
Oh, no, that's probably not such a good idea.
资料表明这些公务员都...
Civil servants have a documented propensity
你知道的  小事一桩  所以...
To, you know, snap, so...
好吧  还是谢谢你
Okay. well, thank you again.
小事一桩  再见
No problem. bye.
再见  老兄
Oh, and bye... bro.
你想什么呢? (谚语中正好影射有潘妮的名字)
Penny for your thoughts.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
我很好
I'm fine.
潘妮很好  和她接吻那家伙也真不错
Penny's fine. the guy she's kissing is really fine.
接吻?  吻哪?  脸颊?  嘴唇?  手?  还是法式舌吻?
Kissing, what kind of kissing? cheeks? lips? chaste? french?
你这是怎么回事啊?
What is wrong with you?
我是个情圣
I'm a romantic.
别告诉我你一下子从毫无希望的迷恋
Don't tell me that your hopeless infatuation
幡然醒悟成一个无理取闹的妒夫
Is devolving into pointless jealousy.
我不是嫉妒  我只是对她比较在意
I'm not jealous. I'm just a little concerned for her.
我不喜欢那家伙的脸
I didn't like the look of the guy.
就因为他比你帅?
Because he looks better than you?
没错  他是有那么点点帅...
He was kind of dreamy.
你和她约会的白日梦被打碎了
At least now you can retrieve the black box
不过至少你还可以从那堆幻想残骸中
From the twisted, smoldering wreckage
取回那个黑匣子
That was once your fantasy of dating her
然后分析下里面的数据
And analyze the data so that you don't crash
来避免再次成为一个爱情傻瓜
Into geek mountain again.
我不同意
I disagree.
爱情不是短跑  是场马拉松
Love is not a sprint, it's a marathon--
是场无情的追击  唯一的终点是她投向你的怀抱
A relentless pursuit that only ends when she falls into your arms...
要不就是用防狼喷雾招呼你
Or hits you with the pepper spray.
我和潘妮结束了
I'm done with penny.
我还是现实点去追个符合我这层次的女人
I'm going to be more realistic and go after someone my own speed.
-比如谁?  -我不知道
- like who? - I don't know...
奥莉维亚·盖革
Olivia geiger.
餐厅里那个双眼慵懒无神的营养学家?
The dietician at the cafeteria with the limp and the lazy eye?
我觉得你没戏
I don't think you have a shot there.
我发现莱斯利·温克最近开始刮腿毛了
I have noticed that leslie winkle recently started shaving her legs.
冬天都要来了
Now given that winter is coming,
她这样只可能是在发求爱信号
One can only assume she's signaling sexual availability.
我不太清楚  你们在同一间实验室
I don't know. you guys work in the same lab.
-所以?  -可能里面有阴谋
- so? - there are pitfalls.
相信我  我就是知道
Trust me, I know.
说到性骚扰的法律条文
When it comes to sexual harassment law,
我是这方面专家  无师自通
I'm a bit of a self-taught expert.
如果我约莱斯利·温克出去
If I were to ask leslie winkle out,
只是吃顿晚饭而已
It would just be for dinner. I'm not going to walk into the lab,
我可不会跑到实验室叫她跳脱衣舞给我看
Ask her to strip naked and dance for me.
那样或许还可以
Oh, then you're probably okay.
-你好  莱斯利  -好  里奥纳德
- hello, leslie. - hi, leonard.
我想做个实验
I'd like to propose an experiment...
先把护目镜戴上
- goggles, leonard. - right.
莱斯利  我想做个实验
I would like to propose an experiment.
等下
Hang on.
我正尝试看看用500千瓦的氧-碘激光器
I'm trying to see how long it takes a 500-kilowatt
要多久才能热好我的杯面
Oxygen iodine laser to heat up my cup a' noodles.
我试了  大概2秒  蔬菜通心粉要2.6秒
I've done it. about two seconds. 2.6 for minestrone.
不管怎样  我一直在想
Anyway, I was thinking more
要和一个神经化学专家一起做个生理-社会的研究
Of a bio-social exploration with a neuro-chemical overlay.
等等  你这是在约我出去吗
Wait, are you asking me out?
我把这称之为是
I was going to characterize it as the modification
用这种类似约会的附加成分
Of our colleague-slash-friendship paradigm
实现从同事关系转化为朋友关系
With the addition of a date-like component,
但我们没必要在专业术语上纠结
But we don't need to quibble over terminology.
什么样的实验?
What sort of experiment?
在这个领域有个公认的模式
There's a generally accepted pattern in this area.
我去接你  然后带你去餐厅
I would pick you up, take you to a restaurant.
再接着看场电影  也许是部由实力演员休·格兰特
Then we would see a movie, probably a romantic comedy
或桑德拉·布洛克出演的浪漫爱情喜剧
Featuring the talents of hugh grant or sandra bullock.
有意思
Interesting. and would you agree
那检验实验成功与否的主要依据
That the primary way we would evaluate either the success
是观察由晚安吻引发的生化反应
Or failure of the date would be
这你没意见吧?
Based on the biochemical reaction during the good night kiss?
心跳速率  荷尔蒙分泌素信息等等  当然是这样
Heart rate, pheromones, etc. yes.
那何不先假定约会一切顺利
Why don't we just stipulate that the date goes well
直接跳到最后可能有变数的那个关键步骤?
And move to the key variable?
-你的意思是现在就吻你?  -是的
- you mean kiss you now? - yes.
能定义下这个吻的参数吗
Can you define the parameters of the kiss?
嘴唇闭合但要浪漫  要薄荷吗
Close-mouthed but romantic. mint?
谢谢
Thank you.
我从3开始倒计时?
I count down from three?
不用  我觉得这得自然而然的开始
No, I think it needs to be spontaneous.
-如何?  -你提出的这个实验
- what do you think? - you proposed the experiment.
你先说
I think you should present your findings first.
很公平
Fair enough.
就好的方面来看  这吻不错
On the plus side, it was a good kiss.
合格的技术  没有多余的唾液
Reasonable technique, no extraneous spittle.
不怎么理想的方面是  毫无感觉
On the other hand, no arousal.
-没感觉吗  -没有
- none? - none.
-谢谢你抽出时间  -谢谢
- thank you for your time. - thank you.
真的一点感觉都没?
None at all?
谢尔顿  如果你是个机器人
Sheldon, if you were a robot,
我知道但你自己不知道...
And I knew and you didn't...
你想我告诉你吗
...would you want me to tell you?
那得看情况
That depends.
如果
When
我知道了
I learn that I'm a robot...
我能够做好自我调整吗
Will I be able to handle it?
大概...不过纵览科幻史  你没戏
Maybe-- although the history of science fiction is not on your side.
好吧  那我来问你
Okay, let me ask you this--
如果我真是个机器人
When I learn that I'm a robot,
我得遵循阿西莫夫机器人三大定律吗
Would I be bound by asimov's three laws of robotics?
貌似你一直没违背过
You might be bound by them right now.
那到是  你有没有伤害过人类?
That's true. have you ever harmed a human being
或看到人类受伤害而袖手旁观?
Or through inaction allowed a human being to come to harm?
-当然没有  -那你有没有伤害过你自己?
- of course not. - have you ever harmed yourself
或者让自己受伤?
Or allowed yourself to be harmed
当然除了在有人类受到伤害的情况下(三大定律内容)
Except in cases where a human being would have been endangered?
-没有  -我闻到机器人的味道了
- well, no. - I smell robot.
怎么了?
Hey, what's going on?
已经断网半个小时了
Internet's been down for half an hour.
另外  谢尔顿也许是个机器人
Also, sheldon may be a robot.
那么和莱斯利怎么样了?
So how'd it go with leslie?
我们试着接吻了  但是地球没有移动
Oh, we tried kissing, but the earth didn't move.
我是说  它还只偏移了该移的383英里
I mean, any more than the 383 miles that it was going to move anyway.
历史要重演了
Oh, I've seen that look before.
闷闷不乐两个星期
This is just going to be two weeks of moping
不断的哼唱冗长乏味的魔鬼之音
And tedious emo songs
还会叫我到楼下的宠物商店去看猫
And calling me to come down to pet stores to look at cats.
我不知道我还受不受的了
I don't know if I can take it.
你可以切断你自己的电源
You could power down.
通常这时候  沃尔斯利都会有办法的
As usual, wolowitz has the solution.
我正好知道有那么个地方...
I happen to know a place
有很多符合里奥纳德条件的女人随他挑
Where there are plenty of eligible women and leonard could have his pick.
记住拉丁里的臀部动作
Remember the latin hips.
肩膀保持不动  然后我们摇摆...
Shoulders stay still, and... we sway.
1  2  3
One, two, three...
5  6  7
...five, six, seven.
我看狄西曼女士是看上你了
I think mrs. tishman's got her eye on you.
我有过这种待遇  她正邀你共舞呢
I've been there. you're in for a treat.
哦  天哪
Oh, good lord.
上帝啊  这真是首好歌
God, that's a good song.
如果你是说你灌了这张唱片是想让我们双双自杀
If you're compiling a mix cd for a double suicide.
哦  希望这个猫抓柱是给你自己用的
Oh, I hope that scratching post is for you.
我知道你在想什么  我考虑到你的哮喘了
I know what you're thinking. I've taken your asthma into account.
圣迭哥有个猫科类基因学家
There's a feline geneticist in san diego
培育一种暴可爱的猫  不易引起过敏
Who's developed the cutest little hypoallergenic calicos.
-听我说  -我想了很多名字
- listen to me... - I've been thinking about names.
我还没决定叫什么  爱因斯坦?  牛顿?
I'm kind of torn between einstein, newton
还是叫莎金氏绒靴
And sergeant fuzzy boots.
你真以为养了只转基因的小猫
Do you really think you can satisfy your need
就能填补你的情感空虚吗
For a relationship with a genetically altered cat?
也许
Maybe.
如果那是只让人爱不释手的可爱小猫
If it's a cute, little, cuddly cat.
得了吧  里奥纳德...
Oh, come on. leonard...
显然是因为潘妮吧
This is obviously about penny.
和那没关系
It doesn't matter.
那女人对我不感兴趣  她拒绝了我
The woman's not interested in me. the woman rejected me.
听着
Look,
我认为你和潘妮上床的几率
I think that you have as much of a chance
就和用一架哈勃望远镜发现
Of having a sexual relationship with penny
每一个太空黑洞中心都有个小人
As the hubble telescope does of discovering
开着手电筒寻找一个断路器
At the center of every black hole
一样渺茫
Is a little man with a flashlight searching for a circuit breaker.
不管怎样
Nevertheless,
我觉得我得和你说明一个问题
I do feel obligated to point out to you
她没有拒绝你
That she did not reject you.
你还从未约过她出去
You did not ask her out.
没错
You're right.
我都没去约过她  我应该去约她
I didn't ask her out. I should ask her out.
不  不  我不是这个意思
No, no, that was not my point.
我的意思是要你别去买只猫回来
My point was don't buy a cat.
不行  但是你说的没错
No, but you're right.
我应该跑过去邀她出去
I should march over there and ask her out.
真是有够棒的  我们即将有只小猫了
Oh, goody, we're getting a cat.
下午好  潘妮  那个...你好
Good afternoon, penny. so, hi... hey.
我是想问有没有安排要去哪就餐?
I was wondering if you had plans for dinner.
你是说今晚晚餐吗
You mean dinner tonight?
就餐这词有其固有的二义性
There is an inherent ambiguity in the word "dinner."
学术上我们可以这样理解
Technically it refers
它是一天中我们吃的最主要的一顿饭
To the largest meal of the day whenever it's consumed.
所以我在此澄清一下  我的这餐指晚饭
So to clarify here, by dinner I mean supper.
-晚饭?  -或者就餐
- supper? - or dinner.
6:30你方便吗  或者你另外定时间
I was thinking 6:30 if you can go. or a different time.
6:30没问题
6:30's great.
真的?
Really?
-太好了  -我喜欢和你们一伙人出去
- great. - I like hanging out with you guys.
我们一伙?
Us guys?
是啊  谢尔顿  霍华德  拉杰  他们都会去吧?
Yeah, you know, sheldon, howard, raj. who all's coming?
他们...
They...
大概都会吧
Might all be there.
或者他们中的某个会去
Or a subset of them might be there.
从代数学来看  有太多的未知数
Algebraically speaking, there are too many unknowns.
比如  万一谢尔顿午饭吃了Quiznos(三明治品牌)
For example, sheldon had quiznos for lunch.
有时候他会觉得吃太撑了
Sometimes he finds that filling, other times he doesn't.
其实这不是Quiznos的错...有很多吃的可以选
It's no fault of quiznos-- they have a varied menu.
好吧  不管怎样  听起来很有意思
Okay, whatever. it sounds like fun.
太好了
Great.
-我们定好时间了吗  -6:30
- did we say a time? - 6:30.
-这时间可以吗  -可以
- and that's still good? - it's fine.
-它没刻在石头上不是非得这时间  -不用  6:30可以
- 'cause it's not carved in stone. - no, 6:30's great.
我去拿凿子
I'll get my chisel.
为什么?
Why?
我要去刻石头...那6:30见
To... carve the... I'll see you at 6:30.
我看上去如何?
How do I look?
能问的更具体点吗
Could you be more specific?
我是不是有点出汗?
Can you tell I'm perspiring a little?
没有  你腋下的月牙形图案很隐蔽
No. the dark crescent-shaped patterns under your arms conceal it nicely.
-你们约了几点?  -6:30
- what time is your date? - 6:30.
太好了
Perfect. that gives you
你还有2个钟头15分钟的时间
Two hours and 15 minutes for that dense molecular cloud
用Aramis(男士化妆品品牌)来分解你那高密度分子云
Of aramis to dissipate.
很明显吗
Is it too much?
对于个橄榄球队的来说很正常
Not if you're a rugby team.
如果你被问起为什么没去
If it should ever come up,
你得回答你在Quiznos
You didn't join us because you stuffed yourself
吃烤鸡肉面加干酪沙司吃撑了
With a chicken carbonara sub at quiznos.
为什么我会和你们一块去?
Why would I join you?
不为什么
No reason.
你知道么  也许这是个馊主意
You know what, maybe this isn't such a good idea.
也不是啊  极有可能
No, well, now there's always the possibility
她会在酒精的作用下神志不清
That alcohol and poor judgment on her part
如此你们就能共度浪漫今宵
Might lead to a nice romantic evening.
没错  酒精  神志不清...确实可能成功
You're right. alcohol, poor judgment-- it could go well.
还有一种可能...
There is the other possibility,  that...
这次约会会引发又一个不愉快的6个月
This date kicks off a rather unpleasant 6 months
两人在走廊里尴尬的擦肩而过
Of the two of you passing awkwardly in the hall,
直到你们其中某人再也受不了而搬去另外一个州
Until one of you breaks down and moves to another zip code.
你在说完"确实可能成功"的时候就该住嘴了
You could've stopped at "it could go well."
如果可以  我会的
If I could've, I would've.
我的意思是  我绝对是个好男人
I mean, I'm a perfectly nice guy.
没理由我们连共进一顿愉快的晚餐都不行
There's no reason we couldn't go and have a lovely dinner,
也许还能来个餐后漫步
Maybe take a walk afterwards,
谈谈我们之间的共同爱好
Talk about things we have in common.
你喜欢陶艺?  我也喜欢
You love pottery? I love pottery!
这里暂停
There's a pause,
接下来发生的大家都猜得到了  我俯身向下  我们接吻了
We both know what's happening. I lean in, we kiss.
先是双方互相试探性的吻
It's a little tentative at first, but then I realize
随后我感觉到她回吻了我  她正轻咬我的下唇
She's kissing me back. she's biting my lower lip!
她想要我  事情就是这么水到渠成了
She wants me! this thing is going the distance!
我们会去做爱  哦  上帝啊  我的上帝
We're going to have sex! oh, god, oh, my god!
现在就开始作爱了?
Is the sex starting now?
我恐慌症发作了
I'm having a panic attack.
好吧  冷静下来
Well then... calm down.
如果可以冷静下来的话  我就不会如此恐慌了
If I could, I wouldn't be having a panic...
所以它才被称作恐慌症
That's why they call it a panic attack.
坐下
Sit down.
就这样  坐好  现在闭上双眼
Yeah, sit down. now close your eyes.
-为什么?  -照做就好了
- why? - just do it.
现在试着激活你的α波
Now try to increase your alpha wave activity.
-什么  -这是生理回馈技术
- what?! - it's a biofeedback technique.
通过控制脑电波来调整放松
It's relaxation through brain wave manipulation.
我在本期刊上读过篇论文
I read a paper about it in journal of american neuroscience.
论证方面稍有欠缺  但我认为基本原理还是对的
It was a little sparsely sourced, but I think the basic science is valid.
好像就放在这附近了
I probably have it here somewhere.
我像在开玩笑吗  再这样子我去不成了
Who am I kidding? I can't go through with this.
你打电话给她帮我取消了吧
You need to call her and cancel.
-我?  -是的
- me? - yes.
-我怎么说?  -不知道  就说我病了
- what should I tell her? - I don't know. tell her I'm sick.
不要那种让她想跑来照顾我的那种病
Not an illness that will make her want to take care of me,
也不要那种严重到让她望而却步的病
But nothing so critical that she'll feel uncomfortable
万一下次我还想要约她出去
Going out with me if I want to try this again.
明白  所以我不可以说你得了性病?
Got it. so I'm assuming nothing venereal?
那我就说你只是做了常规的结肠镜检查
I'll just tell her that you had a routine colonoscopy
还没恢复过来
And haven't quite bounced back.
-把电话给我  -我以为你想取消
- give me the phone. - I thought you wanted to cancel.
不行  我要不去她还会期待你去的
I can't, because if I don't show up she'll still be expecting you.
为什么她会期待我去?
Why would she be expecting me?
别再问我关于这个的问题了
Stop asking me all these questions.
我得再去冲个澡
I need to take another shower.
和其他人约好在这里碰头吗
So are the rest of the guys meeting us here?
哦  是的...不是
Oh, yeah... no.
拉杰和霍华德临时被叫去工作了  谢尔顿...
It turns out that raj and howard had to work, and sheldon...
他做了结肠镜检查还没恢复过来
Had a colonoscopy and he hasn't quite bounced back yet.
我叔叔也刚做完结肠镜检查
My uncle just had a colonoscopy.
开玩笑的吧
You're kidding.
我们是如此的有共同点
Then that's something we have in common.
哪?
How?
在我们的人生中都有那么一个人
We both have people in our lives who...
想要把肠息肉消灭于萌芽中
Want to nip intestinal polyps in the bud.
最近物理界有什么新闻?
So what's new in the world of physics?
没什么
Nothing.
真的没什么?
Really? nothing?
自从30年代发现了弦论以来
Well, with the exception of string theory,
就没什么大事发生了
Not much has happened since the 1930s.
而且弦论还没被证实
And you can't prove string theory.
你最多只能说
At best you can say,
嘿  看啊  我的观点具有内部逻辑相容性
"hey, look, my idea has an internal logical consistency."
这事肯定会被搞定的
Well, I'm sure things will pick up.
芝士蛋糕店那最近有啥新闻?
What's new at the cheesecake factory?
不多
Not much.
有个巧克力酸橙卖的不错
We do have a chocolate key lime that's moving pretty well.
很好
Good.
你那个...
What about your...
走廊里的朋友怎么样了?
Hallway friend?
道格?  哦  我不太清楚
Doug? oh, yeah, I don't know.
我是说  他不错啦  也很风趣  但是...
I mean, you know, he's nice and funny, but...
要先点些饮料吗
Can I get you started with some drinks?
不要
No
-你刚说什么?  但是什么  -我想要杯饮料
- you were saying? but... - I'd like a drink.
还是先说完你关于道格的"但是"吧  我等下会叫她回来的
Just say the "but" thing about doug and then I'll get her back.
我也不知道  反正是我的问题
I don't know, it's just me.
我还没从跟库尔特分手中恢复过来
I'm still getting over this breakup with kurt
和道格之间只是复健性爱
And this thing with doug would just be rebound sex.
别跟我提复健性爱这档事
Don't get me started on rebound sex.
这...我一贯如此
It's just... it's my pattern.
分手  然后找个可爱男生
I break up, then I find some cute guy,
来上36小时毫无意义的...
And then it's just 36 meaningless hours of...
你知道的
You know.
我不确定我明白
I'm not sure that I do.
是36小时连续不断的
Is that one 36-hour experience,
还是分散在
Or is that 36 hours spread out over, say...
一整个美丽夏季里的36个小时?
One glorious summer?
不是  通常是那么一个周末
No, it's usually over a weekend,
相信我  在那之后会很不好受
And trust me, you do not feel good after it.
摩擦过度发炎了  对吧?
Well, chafing, right?
是心情不好
Emotionally.
当然  是的  心理上的发炎
Of course, yeah, emotional chafing.
想不想看点有劲的东西?
Do you want to see something cool?
我不用手拿
I can make this olive go into this glass
就可以让这枚橄榄进杯子
Without touching it.
-怎么弄?  -物理学原理
- how? - physics.
向心力
Centrifugal force.
确切的说  这是离心力
Actually, it's centripetal force,
杯子产生的离心力
Which is an inward force generated by the glass
作用在橄榄上
Acting on the olive...
不好意思
Excuse me.
假设你坐在这颗运动着的橄榄上
If you were riding on the olive,
那么你就是处在一个非惯性参照系中
You'd be in a non-inertial reference frame
并且...
And would...
-你还好吧?  -当然  我没事
- are you okay? - yeah, I'm okay.
你有打翻番茄酱吗
Did you spill ketchup?
-没  -那我就有事了
- no. - I'm not okay.
你确定你不用去急症室吗
You sure you don't want to go to the emergency room?
不用  我很好  血止住了
No, I'm okay. it stopped bleeding.
我知道  但你吐了  不是脑震荡的前兆吗
I know, but you did throw up. isn't that a sign of a concussion?
是啊  但是我还晕车  所以...
Yes. but I get car sick, too, so...
另外  真是对不住你的车
Sorry about your car, by the way.
没事  大部分你都吐车外了
It's fine. you got most of it out the window.
那个骑车的可怜家伙
The poor guy on the bike.
我过的很愉快
I had a nice time.
是的  我也是
Yeah, me, too.
那么  晚安
Well, um, good night.
晚安
Good night.
这算是次约会吗
Was this supposed to be a date?
这次?
This?
不
No.
当然不是  这只是我们和一群人的聚会
Of course not. this was just you and me
只是其他人由于工作原因或肠镜检查
Hanging out with a bunch of guys who didn't show up
没来而已
Cause of work and a colonoscopy.
那好  我只是确认下
Okay, I was just checking.
当我和女孩子约会时
When I take a girl on a date--
我...
And I do--
她会意识到她是在约会
She knows she's been dated.
大写的字母D
Capital d.
黑色粗体  还要加下划线的"Dated"(约会)
Boldface. underlined. da...ted.
也许我真脑震荡了
I think I might have a little concussion.
我要去躺会儿  晚安
I'm gonna go lie down for a while. good night.
那么  你的约会怎么样?
So, how was your date?
棒极了
Awesome!
都是烈酒和酒后糊涂的功劳
Score 1 for liquor and poor jugement.